<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tres Henry</title>
    <link>http://treshenry.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tres Henry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:11:12 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://treshenry.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Diary</title>
      <link>http://treshenry.net/posts/deardiary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 09:11:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://treshenry.net/posts/deardiary/</guid>
      <description>Personal sites are a complicated matter. How do you authentically project your personality into a 2d digital space? This site has gone through nearly as many iterations as I have, which is to say, a lot.
Every personal site has two experiences: the one the public interacts with, and the one you interact with when you manage the site&amp;rsquo;s content. If that interface feels like an I-have-to-sit-down-and-make-an-update type event, then you probably just won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Oracle</title>
      <link>http://treshenry.net/projects/goldenoracle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 15:22:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://treshenry.net/projects/goldenoracle/</guid>
      <description>The Golden Oracle is a book and deck of cards for use in magic and cartomancy. The book and cards are available as a free download from The Golden Oracle and released under the Creative Commons license.
There was a very small initial print run of the cards which are in the hands of a few enthusiasts, however, I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on a second larger print run which will include a premium print of the full-sized cards, a custom rigid box, and an extended version of the second chapter from the book, which contains the card descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Watcher</title>
      <link>http://treshenry.net/projects/thewatcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 15:05:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://treshenry.net/projects/thewatcher/</guid>
      <description>The Watcher is a VR puzzle game passion project that helped me deepen my understanding of VR, HCI, and semiotics. I wrote a lengthy article on its development and lessons learned available on Linkedin: https://tinyurl.com/y3jzs5ae.
Apart from creating all of the game&amp;rsquo;s content (excluding the score), one of the key challenges was communicating purely through the use of symbol and interaction. There is no written language in the game telling the player what to do, why, or how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermes</title>
      <link>http://treshenry.net/projects/hermes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 13:26:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://treshenry.net/projects/hermes/</guid>
      <description>I created a prototype to gather initial market research for an annotation-based notes app concept I&amp;rsquo;m calling Hermes. The prototype covers a small subset of potential functionality—the hotdog of the hotdog stand—but demonstrates the core concept. The prototype is an Electron app written in TypeScript with Vue for rendering and Dexie (IndexedDB) for data. The prototype was a low-fi research tool with no visual design.
Pros   Key/value annotations enable users to create natural taxonomies on-the-fly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>